A Guide to the Asian Cultural Council records, Hong Kong Arts Program, Record Group 6 FA1436
Rockefeller Archive Center
Asian Cultural Council records, Hong Kong Arts Program, Record Group 6
1986-2014
Rockefeller Archive Center
Asian Cultural Council
FA1436
14.36 Cubic Feet 31 letter-size document boxes, 1 half-letter document box, and 1 legal-size document box.
Conditions Governing Access
Open for research with select materials restricted as noted. Brittle or damaged items are available at the discretion of RAC. Researchers interested in accessing digital media (floppy disks, CDs, DVDs, etc.) in this collection must use an access surrogate. The original items may not be accessed because of preservation concerns. To request an access surrogate be made, or if you are unsure if there is an access surrogate, please contact an archivist.
When requesting to view audiovisual material, please refer to the Title and the AV Number (example: AV 1916). Researchers are asked to check the "Restrictions" note for each Title. If a Title does not currently have an access copy, please contact a RAC archivist for further instruction.
Arrangement
The Asian Cultural Council Hong Kong Arts Program files are arranged in three series as follows:
Series 1: External Publicity Materials
Series 2: Photographs
Series 3: Audiovisual Materials
Within series, all records remain in original order.
Other Finding Aids
Other available finding aids describing the Asian Cultural Council records include:
FA427 Asian Cultural Council records, Administrative Files, RG 1
FA1400 Asian Cultural Council records, Conferences, Festivals and Seminars RG 2
FA1401 Asian Cultural Council records, Indo-US Subcommission on Education and Culture, RG 3
FA1402 Asian Cultural Council records, Fellowships and Training Programs, RG 4
FA1403 Asian Cultural Council records, Grants, RG 5
Immediate Source of Acquisition
The Asian Cultural Council records were donated to the RAC in 2010. The Hong Kong Arts Program files were transferred to RAC in 2015, as accession 2015:091.
Biographical / Historical
The Asian Cultural Council is a publicly supported not for profit 501(c)(3) established in 1980 to support cultural exchange between Asia and the United States. The Council carries forward the mission of the Asian Cultural Program of the JDR 3rd Fund, which had been created by JDR 3rd in 1963 and was officially dissolved in July 1979.
The Asian Cultural Council maintains offices in New York, Hong Kong, Manila (Philippines), Taipei (Taiwan) and Tokyo. ACC affiliation with the Rockefeller Brothers Fund began in 1991, enabling the Council to reduce administrative overhead and devote a larger percentage of its funds directly to grants and program development.
Scope and Contents
Photographs, program booklets, publicity materials and videos documenting the events, programs, awards, and grantees of the Hong Kong Arts Program from 1986 through 2014.
- External Publicity Materials, 1
  - Asian Cultural Council Hong Kong Newsletter, 1995; 1998-2014 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - ACC Corporate Pamphlets (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - ACC Corporate Pamphlets - ACC Hong Kong Arts Program, 1986-1996 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - ACC Events - Invitation Cards - ACC Hong Kong Arts Program Tenth Anniversary, 1996 November 22 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - ACC Events - Invitation Cards - Twenty Years in Hong Kong, 2008 January 18 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - ACC Events - Invitation Cards - Natvar Bhavsar, 2010 February 22 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - ACC Events - Invitation Cards - Asian Cultural Council In the Heart of the Arts, 2010 November 9 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - ACC Events - Invitation Cards - Selected Asian Cultural Council Fellows: Then and Now works by Wei Ligang, Wei Qingji, Zhang Jianjun, 2011 May 12 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - ACC Events - Invitation Cards - The Hidden Dimensions of Architects, 2011 November 3 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - ACC Events - Invitation Cards - Intersections - Selected Asian Cultural Council Fellows Wucius Wong, Fiona Wong, Hung Keung, 2012 May 14 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - ACC Events - Invitation Cards - 2012 ACC Annual Fellowship Awards Dinner, 2012 October 18 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - ACC Events - Invitation Cards - Midori Moments, 2013 May 26 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - ACC Events - Invitation Cards - Hon Chi Fun?s Perspective at 91 and the 2013 ACC Hong Kong Fellowship Award Ceremony, 2013 September 10 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - ACC Events - Invitation Cards - ACC Special Event: Cai Guo-Qiang: The Ninth Wave, 2014 October 20 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - ACC Events - Invitation Cards - On Stage with Jin Xing, 2014 October 26 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - ACC Events - Program Booklets - On Stage with Lin Cho-Liang, 1988 November 12 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - ACC Events - Program Booklets - On Stage with Yo-Yo Ma, 1989 November 14 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - ACC Events - Program Booklets - On Stage with Wang Jian, 1991 November 2 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - ACC Events - Program Booklets - ACC Works by Hong Kong Grantees, 1994 June 16-29 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - ACC Events - Program Booklets - ACC Hong Kong Arts Program Tenth Anniversary Gala, 1996 November 22 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - ACC Events - Program Booklets - Distinguished Speakers in the Arts: Howard, 2002 January 25-28 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - ACC Events - Program Booklets - Crossing Boundaries Works by ACC Fellows 2005, 2005 September 26-October 2 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - ACC Events - Program Booklets - Twenty Years in Hong Kong, 1987-2007 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - ACC Events - Program Booklets - ACC celebrates Twenty Years in Hong Kong, 2008 January 18 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - ACC Events - Program Booklets - ACC Annual Fellowship Awards 2009, 2009 November 5 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - ACC Events - Program Booklets - ACC Annual Fellowship Awards 2010, 2010 November 9 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - ACC Events - Program Booklets - Chance Machine, 2011 May 26-29 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - ACC Events - Program Booklets - ACC Annual Fellowship Awards 2011, 2011 November 3 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - ACC Events - Program Booklets - The Hidden Dimensions of Architects, 2011 November 4-7 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - ACC Events - Program Booklets - Midori Moments, 2013 May 26 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - ACC Events - Program Booklets - Hon Chi Fun's Perspective at 91, 2013 September 9-29 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - ACC Events - Program Booklets - On Stage with Jin Xing, 2014 October 26-27 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - ACC Events - Grantee Booklet - Still Building Young Architects? Award Recipients, 1990-2010 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - ACC Grantee Book - ADF and I by Yang Meiqi, 2010 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - ACC Events - Videos and Photos - ACC-Hong Kong: 1987 East West Encounter, 1987 October 14; DVD (Box 1, Folder 10)
    Conditions Governing Access
    Researchers interested in accessing digital media (floppy disks, CDs, DVDs, etc.) in this collection must use an access surrogate. The original items may not be accessed because of preservation concerns. Access copy currently unavailable. Please contact a RAC archivist for further instruction.
  - ACC Events - Videos and Photos - ACC-Hong Kong: 1991 On Stage with Wang Jian, 1991 November 2; DVD (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - ACC Events - Videos and Photos - ACC-Hong Kong: 1994 Fundraising Ball, 1994 December 2; DVD (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - ACC Events - Videos and Photos - ACC-Hong Kong:1996- Tenth Anniversary Gala, 1996 November 22; DVD (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - ACC Events - Videos and Photos - ACC-Hong Kong: 2000 Award Reception I, 2000 June 26; DVD (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - ACC Events - Videos and Photos - ACC-Hong Kong: 2000 Award Reception II, 2000 June 26; DVD (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - ACC Events - Videos and Photos - ACC-Hong Kong: 2002 Award Reception, 2002 June 20; DVD (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - ACC Events - Videos and Photos - ACC-Hong Kong: 2002 Board Trip to China from Bibo Liang-Final Version, 2002 November 3-10; DVD (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - ACC Events - Videos and Photos - ACC: 2002 2nd Forum on Arts and Culture in Mekong Region, 2002 February 17-23; DVD (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - ACC Events - Videos and Photos - ACC-Hong Kong: 2003 Award Reception, 2003 June 27; DVD (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - ACC Events - Videos and Photos - ACC-Hong Kong: 18 Years in Hong Kong (1985-2003), 2003 December 5; VCD (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - ACC Events - Videos and Photos - ACC-Hong Kong: 2004 Award Reception, 2004 June 24; DVD (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - ACC Events - Videos and Photos - ACC-New York: 2004 ACC 40th Anniversary Gala, 2004 November 10; DVD (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - ACC Events - Videos and Photos - ACC-New York: 2004 ACC 40th Anniversary Pre-Gala Party, 2004 November 10; DVD (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - ACC Events - Videos and Photos - ACC-New York: 2004 ACC 40th Anniversary Pre-Event Evening, 2004 November 10; DVD (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - ACC Events - Videos and Photos - ACC-New York: 2004 ACC 40th Anniversary Going to Dinner, 2004 November 10; DVD (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - ACC Events - Videos and Photos - ACC-New York: 2004 ACC 40th Anniversary Gala Performance, 2004 November 10; DVD (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - ACC Events - Videos and Photos - ACC-New York: 2004 ACC Museum Visit, 2004 November 10; DVD (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - ACC Events - Videos and Photos - ACC-Hong Kong: Grantee Shooting in HK- Pak Sheung Chuen and Margaret Cogswell, 2006 April 2; DVD (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - ACC Events - Videos and Photos - ACC-Hong Kong: Grantee Shooting in HK- Barbara London and Olivia Yan, 2006 April 28; DVD (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - ACC Events - Videos and Photos - ACC-Hong Kong: Grantee Shooting in HK- Lung Heung Wing, 2006 April 28; DVD (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - ACC Events - Videos and Photos - ACC-Hong Kong: Grantee Shooting in HK- Hon Chi Fun and Chen Rong (Part I), 2006 April 30; DVD (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - ACC Events - Videos and Photos - ACC-Hong Kong: Grantee Shooting in HK- Chen Rong (Part II) and Alito Alessi (Part I), 2006 April 30; DVD (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - ACC Events - Videos and Photos - ACC-Hong Kong: Grantee Shooting in HK- Alito Alessi (Part II), 2006 April 30; DVD (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - ACC Events - Videos and Photos - ACC-Hong Kong: Grantee Shooting in HK- Jenny So, ACC-HK office, Carol Lin, Kenneth Fung, Katusha Tsui, 2006 May 2; DVD (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - ACC Events - Videos and Photos - ACC-Hong Kong: ACC Photo Montage (RAW Version) for Chateau Event, 2006 May 22; DVD (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - ACC Events - Videos and Photos - ACC-Hong Kong: Grantee Trip- Dikdik Sayahdikumullah Part I, 2006 July; DVD (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - ACC Events - Videos and Photos - ACC-Hong Kong: Grantee Trip- Dikdik Part II and Hung Keung, 2006 July; DVD (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - ACC Events - Videos and Photos - ACC-Hong Kong: Interview with Valerie Rockefeller in NY, 2006 September 7; DVD (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - ACC Events - Videos and Photos - ACC-Hong Kong: Grantee (2005) Trip - PowerPoint Presentation, 2006 October 26; DVD (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - ACC Events - Videos and Photos - ACC-Hong Kong: 2006 Award Reception and Exhibition Part I, 2006 October 26; DVD (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - ACC Events - Videos and Photos - ACC-Hong Kong: 2006 Award Reception and Dinner Part II, 2006 October 26; DVD (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - ACC Events - Videos and Photos - ACC-TAIPEI: 2006 ACC Trip to Taipei, 2006 November; DVD (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - ACC Events - Videos and Photos - ACC-Hong Kong: Grantee Shooting in HK- Hung Keung, 2007 March; DVD (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - ACC Events - Videos and Photos - ACC-Hong Kong: 2007 ACC Documentary Film- FINAL with Music, 2007 June; DVD (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - ACC Events - Videos and Photos - ACC - New York: Excellence and Exchange in the Arts, 2008 December 3; DVD (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - ACC Events - Videos and Photos - ACC-Hong Kong: Network of Asian Artists (55 grantees), 2004 June 24; CD (Box 1, Folder 11)
- Photographs, 1986-2006; 2
  Photographs
  - 1986 ACC Events - ACC-Hong Kong Opening at Madarin Hotel, Slides (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - 1986 ACC Events - ACC-Hong Kong Opening Reception (Box 2, Folder 3A)
  - 1986 ACC Events - ACC-HK Opening - Mrs. Rockefeller at APA. Presentation at Art Center, Slides (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - 1987 ACC Events - East West Encounter, Photo print and slides (Box 2, Folder 5-7)
  - 1987 ACC Events - Friends' Trip to Japan, Photo print (Box 2, Folder 8)
  - 1987 ACC Grantees - BAT Grantees, Photo print (Box 2, Folder 9)
  - 1987 ACC Grantees - Ko Tin Lung, Photo print (Box 2, Folder 10)
  - 1987 ACC Grantees - Lau Kin Wai, Photo print (Box 2, Folder 11)
  - 1988 ACC Events - On Stage with Lin Cho-Liang, Photo print and slides (Box 2, Folder 12-14)
  - 1988 ACC Events - On Stage with Lin Cho-Liang, Photo print and slides (Box 3, Folder 1-4)
  - 1988 ACC Events - Grantees and Friends Meeting, Slides (Box 3, Folder 5)
  - 1988 ACC Grantees Photos - BAT Grantees, Photo print (Box 3, Folder 6)
  - 1988 ACC Grantees Photos - Benny Chia, Photo print (Box 3, Folder 7)
  - 1988 ACC Grantees Photos - Eric Pun, Sally Wong, Dorothy Wong, Photo print and slides (Box 3, Folder 8)
  - 1988 ACC Grantees Photos - Dimon Liu, Photo print (Box 3, Folder 9)
  - 1988 ACC Grantees Photos - Vicki Ooi, Photo print (Box 3, Folder 10)
  - 1988 ACC Grantees Photos - Tong Kin Woon, Photo print (Box 3, Folder 11)
  - 1988 ACC Grantees Photos - James Watt, Photo print (Box 3, Folder 12)
  - 1988 ACC Grantees Photos - Yan Mui, Photo print (Box 3, Folder 13)
  - 1988 ACC Grantess Photos - Wucius Wang, Photo print (Box 3, Folder 14)
  - 1988 ACC Grantees Photos - Kwok Hiu Wah, Photo print (Box 3, Folder 14A)
  - 1988 ACC Grantees Photos - John Fung, Photo print and slides (Box 3, Folder 15)
  - 1988 ACC Grantees Photos - Chuang Che, Photo print (Box 3, Folder 16)
  - 1989 ACC Events Photos - On Stage with Yo-Yo Ma, Photo print (Box 4, Folder 1)
  - 1989 ACC Events Photos - Grantees and Friends Meeting, Photo print (Box 4, Folder 2)
  - 1989 ACC Events Photos - Friends' Trip to Hangzhou, Photo print (Box 4, Folder 3)
  - 1989 ACC Grantees Photos - Philip Tat Chiu Fok, Photo print and slides (Box 4, Folder 4)
  - 1989 ACC Grantees Photos - Augustine Chiu Yu Mok, Photo print (Box 4, Folder 5)
  - 1989 ACC Grantees Photos - Pun Siu Fai, Photo print (Box 4, Folder 6)
  - 1989 ACC Grantees Photos - BAT Grantees, Photo print (Box 4, Folder 7)
  - 1989 ACC Grantees Photos - Francis Ka Kuen Leung, Photo print (Box 4, Folder 8)
  - 1989 ACC Grantees Photos - Mui Cheuk Yin, Photo print and slides (Box 4, Folder 9)
  - 1989 ACC Grantees Photos - Grace Lo, Photo print and slides (Box 4, Folder 10)
  - 1989 ACC Grantees Photos - Choi Yan Chi, Photo print (Box 4, Folder 11)
  - 1989 ACC Grantees Photos - Sam Ang-Sam, Photo print (Box 4, Folder 12)
  - 1989 ACC Grantees Photos - Grantees Party, Photo print (Box 4, Folder 13)
  - 1990 ACC Events Photos - Grantees and Friends Meeting, Photo print (Box 4, Folder 14)
  - 1990 ACC Events Photos - Friends' Trip to Japan, Photo print (Box 4, Folder 15)
  - 1990 ACC Grantees Photos - Jacky Yu, Photo print (Box 5, Folder 1)
  - 1990 ACC Grantees Photos - Psyche Chui Yuen Fan, Photo print (Box 5, Folder 2)
  - 1990 ACC Grantees Photos - Wan Man-Kit, Photo print (Box 5, Folder 3)
  - 1990 ACC Grantees Photos - Leung Ping Kwan, Photo print (Box 5, Folder 4)
  - 1990 ACC Grantees Photos - Comyn Mo, Photo print (Box 5, Folder 5)
  - 1990 ACC Grantees Photos - Nelson Chu, Photo print (Box 5, Folder 6)
  - 1990 ACC Grantees Photos - BAT Grantees, Photo print (Box 5, Folder 7)
  - 1990 ACC Grantees Photos - Grantees Party, Photo print (Box 5, Folder 8)
  - 1990 ACC Grantees Photos - 1987-1990 BAT Grantees Group Photos, Photo print (Box 5, Folder 9)
  - 1991 ACC Events Photos - On Stage with Wang Jian, Photo print (Box 5, Folder 10)
  - 1991 ACC Events Photos, Photo print (Box 5, Folder 11)
  - 1991 ACC Events Photos - Grantees and Friends Meeting, Photo print (Box 5, Folder 12)
  - 1991 ACC Events Photos - Friends' Trip to Indonesia, Photo print (Box 5, Folder 13)
  - 1991 ACC Grantees Photos - Taiwan Grantees, Photo print (Box 5, Folder 14)
  - 1991 ACC Grantees Photos - Chow Chi Chung, Slides (Box 5, Folder 15)
  - 1991 ACC Grantees Photos - Raymond To, Negatives only (Box 5, Folder 16)
  - 1991 ACC Grantees Photos - Victor Lai, Photo print (Box 5, Folder 17)
  - 1991 ACC Grantees Photos - Diana Pao, Photo print and slides (Box 5, Folder 18)
  - 1991 ACC Grantees Photos - Ellen Pau, Photo print (Box 6, Folder 1)
  - 1991 ACC Grantees Photos - Tommy Wong, Photo print (Box 6, Folder 2)
  - 1992 ACC Events Photos - Grantees and Friends Meeting, Photo print (Box 6, Folder 3)
  - 1992 ACC Events Photos - Friends' Trip to Guangzhou, Photo print (Box 6, Folder 4-7)
  - 1992 ACC Events Photos - Friends' Trip to Thailand, Photo print (Box 6, Folder 8)
  - 1992 ACC Grantees Photos - Chau Hing Wah, Photo print and slides (Box 6, Folder 9)
  - 1992 ACC Grantees Photos - Cheung Tat Ming, Photo print (Box 6, Folder 10)
  - 1992 ACC Grantees Photos - BAT Grantees, Photo print and slides (Box 6, Folder 11)
  - 1992 ACC Grantees Photos - Lewis So, Photo print and slides (Box 6, Folder 12)
  - 1992 ACC Grantees Photos - Simon Wong, Photo print and slides (Box 6, Folder 13)
  - 1992 ACC Grantees Photos - Jackson Tse, Photo print and slides (Box 6, Folder 14)
  - 1992 ACC Grantees Photos - Oscar Ho, Photo print (Box 6, Folder 15)
  - 1993 ACC Events Photos - Grantees and Friends Meeting, Photo print (Box 7, Folder 1)
  - 1993 ACC Events Photos - Hopewell Highway Project Charity on Wheels, Photo print (Box 7, Folder 2)
  - 1993 ACC Grantees Photos - Almond Chu, Photo print and slides (Box 7, Folder 3)
  - 1993 ACC Grantees Photos - Chu Hing Wah, Photo print and slides (Box 7, Folder 4)
  - 1993 ACC Grantees Photos - May Fung, Photo print and slides (Box 7, Folder 5)
  - 1993 ACC Grantees Photos - Cecilia Ho, Photo print (Box 7, Folder 6)
  - 1993 ACC Grantees Photos - Allen Lam, Photo prints and slides (Box 7, Folder 6A)
  - 1993 ACC Grantees Photos - Raymond Leung and Lung Heung Wing, Photo prints and slides (Box 7, Folder 7)
  - 1993 ACC Grantees Photos - William Liu, Slides (Box 7, Folder 8)
  - 1993 ACC Grantees Photos - Sydney Pun, Photo prints and slides (Box 7, Folder 9)
  - 1993 ACC Grantees Photos - Wong Sun Keung, Photo prints and slides (Box 7, Folder 10)
  - 1993 ACC Grantees Photos - Wong Wo Bik, Photo prints and slides (Box 7, Folder 11)
  - 1993 ACC Grantees Photos - BAT Luncheon, Photo print (Box 7, Folder 12)
  - 1994 ACC Events Photos - Shall We Dance Fundraising Ball at Government House, 1994 December 2; Photo print (Box 7, Folder 13-14)
  - 1994 ACC Events Photos - Shall We Dance Fundraising Ball at Government House Album 1, 1994 December 2; Photo print (Box 8, Folder 1-2)
  - 1994 ACC Events Photos - Shall We Dance Fundraising Ball at Government House Album 2, 1994 December 2; Photo print (Box 8, Folder 3-4)
  - 1994 Events Photos - Shall We Dance Fundraising Ball at Government House Album 3, 1994 December 2; Photo print (Box 8, Folder 5)
  - 1994 Events Photos - Shall We Dance Fundraising Ball at Government House Album 3, 1994 December 2; Photo print (Box 9, Folder 1)
  - 1994 ACC Events Photos - Grantees and Friends Meeting, Photo print (Box 9, Folder 2)
  - 1994 ACC Grantees Photos - Chan Ming Long, Photo print (Box 9, Folder 3)
  - 1994 ACC Grantees Photos - Kung Chi Shing, Photo print (Box 9, Folder 4)
  - 1994 ACC Grantees Photos - Kwan Pun Leung, Photo print (Box 9, Folder 5)
  - 1994 ACC Grantees Photos - Law Wing Fai, Photo print (Box 9, Folder 6)
  - 1994 ACC Grantees Photos - Harold Mok, Photo print (Box 9, Folder 7)
  - 1994 ACC Grantees Photos - Poly Ng, Photo print (Box 9, Folder 8)
  - 1994 ACC Grantees Photos - Tong Shiu Wai, Photo print (Box 9, Folder 9)
  - 1994 ACC Grantees Photos - Andy Wong, Photo print (Box 9, Folder 10)
  - 1994 ACC Grantees Photos - Holly Lee-Wong, Photo print (Box 9, Folder 11)
  - 1994 ACC Grantees Photos - Regina Yung, Photo print (Box 9, Folder 12)
  - 1994 ACC Grantees Photos - Chen Wei Ya, Photo print (Box 9, Folder 13)
  - 1994 ACC Grantees Photos - Chan Yan Yan, Photo print (Box 9, Folder 14)
  - 1994 ACC Grantees Photos - BAT Grantees, Photo print (Box 9, Folder 15)
  - 1994 ACC Grantees Photos - Chan Lai Kiu and Zhuang Weimin, Photo print (Box 9, Folder 16)
  - 1994 ACC Grantees Photos - FC Exhibition: Hon Chi Fun, Photo print (Box 9, Folder 17)
  - 1994 ACC Grantees Photos - FC Exhibition: Victor Lai, Photo print (Box 9, Folder 18)
  - 1994 ACC Grantees Photos - FC Exhibition: Wucius Wong, Photo print (Box 9, Folder 19)
  - 1994 ACC Grantees Photos - FC Exhibition: Almond Chu, Photo print (Box 9, Folder 20)
  - 1994 ACC Grantees Photos - FC Exhibition: Kwan Pun Leung, Photo print (Box 9, Folder 21)
  - 1994 ACC Grantees Photos - FC Exhibition: Holly Lee-Wong, Photo print (Box 9, Folder 22)
  - 1994 ACC Grantees Photos - FC Exhibition: John Fung, Photo print (Box 9, Folder 23)
  - 1994 ACC Grantees Photos - FC Exhibition: Chu Hing Wah, Photo print (Box 9, Folder 24)
  - 1995 ACC Events Photos - Friends' Trip to Taiwan, Photo print (Box 10, Folder 1)
  - 1995 ACC Grantees Photos - 1995 Grantees, Photo print (Box 10, Folder 2)
  - 1995 ACC Grantees Photos - Stephen Yip, Photo print (Box 10, Folder 3)
  - 1995 ACC Grantees Photos - BAT Grantees, Photo print (Box 10, Folder 4)
  - 1995 ACC Grantees Photos - Abby Chan, Photo print (Box 10, Folder 5)
  - 1995 ACC Grantees Photos - Chin Kwok Wai, Photo print (Box 10, Folder 6)
  - 1995 ACC Grantees Photos - Rocelia Fung, Photo print (Box 10, Folder 7)
  - 1995 ACC Grantees Photos - Anna Chan, Photo print (Box 10, Folder 8)
  - 1995 ACC Grantees Photos - So Hing Keung, Photo print (Box 10, Folder 9)
  - 1995 ACC Grantees Photos - Xing Liang, Photo print (Box 10, Folder 10)
  - 1996 ACC Events Photos - ACC-Hong Kong 10th Anniversary Gala, Photo print (Box 10, Folder 11)
  - 1996 ACC Grantees Photos - Victor Ma, Photo print (Box 10, Folder 12)
  - 1996 ACC Grantees Photos - Victor Ma and Mandy Yim, Photo print (Box 10, Folder 13)
  - 1996 ACC Grantees Photos - Mandy Yim, Photo print (Box 10, Folder 14)
  - 1996 ACC Grantees Photos - Cheung Chi Wai, Photo print (Box 10, Folder 15)
  - 1996 ACC Grantees Photos - Hsin Chong Luncheon, Photo print (Box 10, Folder 16)
  - 1996 ACC Grantees Photos - BAT Grantees, Photo print (Box 10, Folder 17)
  - 1997 ACC Events Photos - China Grantees Meetings, Photo print (Box 10, Folder 18)
  - 1997 ACC Events Photos - Friends' Trip to Shanghai, Photo print (Box 10, Folder 19)
  - 1997 ACC Grantees Photos - Mark Chan, Negatives only (Box 11, Folder 1)
  - 1997 ACC Grantees Photos - Warren Leung, Photo print (Box 11, Folder 2)
  - 1997 ACC Grantees Photos - Gary Chang, Photo print (Box 11, Folder 3)
  - 1997 ACC Grantees Photos - Marie Hung, Photo print (Box 11, Folder 4)
  - 1997 ACC Grantees Photos - Yeung Hei, Photo print (Box 11, Folder 5)
  - 1997 ACC Grantees Photos - Tang Shu Wing, Photo print (Box 11, Folder 6)
  - 1997 ACC Grantees Photos - BAT Grantees, Photo print (Box 11, Folder 7)
  - 1997 ACC Grantees Photos - Huang Yi-Ru, Photo print (Box 11, Folder 8)
  - 1997 ACC Grantees Photos - Wang Min, Photo print and slides (Box 11, Folder 9)
  - 1997 ACC Grantees Photos - Li Zhongmou, Photo print and slides (Box 11, Folder 10)
  - 1998 ACC Grantees Photos - Phoebe Man, Photo print (Box 11, Folder 11)
  - 1998 ACC Grantees Photos - Wendy Wong, Photo print (Box 11, Folder 12)
  - 1998 ACC Grantees Photos - Martin Fung, Photo print (Box 11, Folder 13)
  - 1998 ACC Grantees Photos - Fiona Wong, Photo print (Box 11, Folder 14)
  - 1998 ACC Grantees Photos - Annie Ho, Photo print and slides (Box 11, Folder 15)
  - 1998 ACC Grantees Photos - Zhou Chunyu, Photo print (Box 11, Folder 16)
  - 1998 ACC Grantees Photos - Arts with the Disabled Association, Slides (Box 11, Folder 17)
  - 1998 ACC Grantees Photos - Dance HK-NY, Slides (Box 11, Folder 18)
  - 1998 ACC Grantees Photos - Image Lab-Mui Cheuk Yin, Slides (Box 11, Folder 19)